var daejeon=[
{
	"city": "daejeon",
	"author": "被拉",
	"question": "马日他怕 狗唱",
	"answer": "Martabak kacang",
	"hint": "Everyone's all time fav indonesian food/snacks"
},
{
	"city": "daejeon",
	"author": "Cannot laa (in hokkien)",
	"question": "Alright 肉 안미안",
	"answer": "I like raw onion",
	"hint": "This sentence contradicts your faith on a certain food"
},
{
	"city": "daejeon",
	"author": "John Kim",
	"question": "What will happen when Tom and Jerry make ice cream?",
	"answer": "Ben & Jerrys",
	"hint": "You can buy it at GS25."
}

];

var bandung=[
{
	"city": "bandung",
	"author": "Coach",
	"question": "Cue cheese angry erm",
	"answer": "Cookies and cream",
	"hint": "It's a type of flavour!"
},
{
	"city": "bandung",
	"author": "알빈",
	"question": "Eye ammo knicker",
	"answer": "I am Monica",
	"hint": "Who are you?"
},
{
	"city": "bandung",
	"author": "Ewwinnnn",
	"question": "Hanzo 파",
	"answer": "Hans oppa",
	"hint": "♥️"
}
];

var penang=[
{
	"city": "penang",
	"author": "your roommate :)",
	"question": "For Initial Eyes",
	"answer": "Finish your rice",
	"hint": "Mum says can't waste food!"
},
{
	"city": "penang",
	"author": "en zhen",
	"question": "mee juice worm itchy",
	"answer": "miss you so much",
	"hint": "보고싶다"
},
{
	"city": "penang",
	"author": "crazy me",
	"question": "current lamp 아",
	"answer": "korean drama",
	"hint": "something addicted, but takes time"
}
];

var kl=[
{
	"city": "kl",
	"author": "Hui Zhi",
	"question": "oui la vie eurre",
	"answer": "I love you",
	"hint": "what hans says to monica"
},
{
	"city": "kl",
	"author": "Hui zhi lol",
	"question": "Sawadeet tulanee trai",
	"answer": "Sweet 23",
	"hint": "Age"
},
{
	"city": "kl",
	"author": "hz lv ec",
	"question": "How many people are there in your 22nd birthday? (Yes, find the picture~~)",
	"answer": "22",
	"hint": "나는 너를 모르지만 나는 ____를 느끼고있다 (lyrics)"
},
];